The main topic I want to talk about today may be about the possibility of digital fashion in the international fashion market and some future possibilities.
Because I have been working overseas, I know more about the acceptance of digital fashion and the cloud software.
And what are the practical applications in the actual production process.
First of all, I will talk about this from the perspective of a more traditional fashion industry.
Because I am also working in a more traditional fashion brand.
In fact, digital fashion has begun to integrate into the normal work process of many traditional fashion brands.
I will make a specific explanation later.
Secondly, I will talk about some cases.
It is my startup company, ALTA.
Our company mainly uses digital fashion, cloud and other digital modeling software.
To promote digital fashion.
It is used to copy some cultural objects or some archival fashion.
It refers to the digital clothing of some files.
Many traditional fashion brands have several decades of history.
And then these have a lot of clothes from the past fashion shows.
In fact, it is difficult to preserve.
We also hope to provide them with a possibility to unlock the value of this historical culture through some digital solutions.
Finally, I will talk about some relatively new industrial directions.
Like digital fashion.
In fact,
There are a lot of new things under this big fashion lens.
For example, some fashion weeks like digital fashion.
Then some fashion shows.
Even some digital fashion movies, etc.
And then there are some concepts of the virtual universe that were more popular a few years ago.
And then here I will also make a few cases of sharing.
The last one is a Q&A.
I hope to have a chance to communicate with you.
Let's start with the digital upgrade of the traditional fashion industry.
I will focus on two aspects.
The first aspect is about the actual digital upgrade in our production process.
The second process may be about how we use some CGI to help some sales.
Or some social media operations.
This is a general overview of how we conduct production processes in traditional fashion companies.
Because I believe that many of my friends may also learn design themselves.
I won't go into too much detail about this.
This is a very big project.
In general, we will have a design idea first.
Then we will find the right fabric.
Then we will produce a tech pack that can match the supplier or the factory.
This is a technical package.
Then we will make the traditional pattern.
During the process of making the pattern, you will find that
From the visual to the final pattern,
It actually requires a lot of trial and error.
During the process of making the sample,
Usually it may take three or even five samples.
In order to achieve the final result,
We can produce a perfect sample.
Now we may start to use 3D modeling in this kind of fashion brand.
Then, for example, we are in the stage of plating.
At the stage of plating,
First of all, many brands have already started to use digital plating.
Of course, this may not be completely true.
All my products use digital plating.
Because especially when I work at Vivian,
We have a lot of plating.
It is through traditional examples.
It is through traditional ways of plating.
This is why you can see a lot of our clothing.
There may be a lot of creases or asymmetrical structures.
Of course, there is also a large part of the pattern.
We will transform it into a digital pattern after plating.
Then take it to CLO and adjust it.
Make some upgrades.
Then reach the final production.
This process actually saves us a lot of time.
The cost of the fabric, etc.
Then we can quickly
From 3D visual support,
We can achieve a perfect production effect.
In addition, it also starts from a production point of view.
This is another market brand I worked with before.
It is also a British underwear brand.
A project to cooperate.
They actually use this 3D vision
To help them make some fabric choices.
Can you see that there is a three-dimensional rendering in it?
In the right side.
I can't see the interaction.
Then I will directly reveal the answer here.
In fact, it's all rendering.
Including these very detailed laser effects.
Then include the small to the small on the underwear.
Some of the small fabric buttons, etc.
All completed in CLO.
Modeling and rendering.
As for them,
In fact, they have been on their own e-commerce platform.
To use a lot of this rendering picture.
Directly as a product picture.
To help this kind of user to understand this style.
Here I put a small recording file.
You can see this part on the left.
Like in the previous picture.
We can achieve this kind of front and back.
It's a completely separate rendering picture.
In fact, it's through you.
Added a flat panel like this.
When rendering, it's done.
In this way, it can help you very well.
Especially this kind of laser.
It's a kind of translucent effect.
Then you look from the front.
When you look at this underwear.
It will not be affected by the structure behind it at all.
Including if you want to see the details behind it.
You don't have to go to the front.
This kind of more complex laser effect.
The other one is coloring.
Because Clove has such a function.
You can use multiple colors in the same file.
This is a very good case.
We can use the same product.
Then directly in the same file.
To develop different colors.
Next, let's come to our second part.
This part is about my own startup company.
And then how we use digital fashion.
To unlock this kind of historical cultural value.
First, give you some background information.
Because in fact, we who learn fashion.
Or anyone related to art.
Will understand.
We now have a lot of innovation.
In fact, it is based on the history.
Many designers will find inspiration from history.
To do the current research.
Looking back.
In fact, in addition to what we have now.
After the industrial revolution.
This existing fashion industry.
Fashion industry.
Looking forward.
In fact, for a long time.
From ancient Egypt.
Ancient China.
India, etc.
Each period has its own fashion.
But at that time.
We don't call it a fashion industry.
At that time.
It may be some different national customs.
Some research of different fabrics.
Some shrinkage.
Or any kind of craft.
Here.
We often in modern fashion design.
To gather a lot.
Inspiration from the past history.
The whole world.
I believe it is built on history.
Especially a lot of luxury brands.
They have a very rich history heritage.
But this heritage.
In fact, it is often very difficult.
To unlock this value.
Why do I say that?
Here I have a case.
Like Mugler.
It is a French.
Very traditional.
This kind of high-end fashion brand.
He from.
He in 2025.
If I remember correctly.
He held an exhibition in the United States.
Then he in the past.
In the 50 years of history.
Has designed more than.
More than 10 million.
More than 10 million pieces of clothing.
From each of his seasons.
But in his archive.
May be existing.
I can't say this.
But in his own.
In the database.
Existing.
It must be a very small amount.
He can't have one.
Enough space.
To store.
More than 10,000 sets of clothing.
So he held this exhibition.
In the past two years.
When.
This should be considered.
The biggest exhibition he has held in the past few years.
He exhibited 150 pieces of clothing.
Exhibited seven months.
But this is just a short seven months.
Compared to the history of these 50 years.
And the 10,000 sets of history.
This kind of archive.
This is just a very, very small.
A puzzle.
In this entire archive.
So.
We are thinking.
How can we help.
These traditional brands.
To protect.
Better protection.
And better inheritance.
These historical clothes.
I believe.
We are entering.
A new era.
We can use.
The rich historical value of the brand.
And now.
The digital audience.
To make a deep interaction.
Because we are now.
More and more.
To.
You know.
Contact a lot of information.
Is online.
For example.
This exhibition.
It's in New York.
I may not be able to buy a ticket immediately.
Can't be in these seven months.
And so on.
Fly over in time.
To get to know.
But if we have.
The corresponding online exhibition.
Digital exhibition.
So I believe.
Everyone is willing.
To click on this link.
Take a look.
To get to know.
Here.
Is a case.
I gave.
We.
From the past.
And.
How.
Through.
These digital methods.
To unlock.
The infinite possibilities of the future.
Here.
You can see.
This.
Rotating.
Small model.
In fact.
This is also.
I.
To restore.
The.
Mugler.
They.
This is.
Parker Ray.
Band.
They.
A long time ago.
In the 1970s.
One.
Is.
A typical.
One.
Is.
We.
Through.
Digital modeling.
To restore.
One.
From.
We.
Is.
A phoenix in Chinese history.
That.
This phoenix.
I believe.
Everyone.
Is.
Many.
Have seen.
The same.
Is.
Style.
Or.
Similar.
Type.
Some.
Is.
Phoenix.
In this museum.
That.
Is.
To.
Use.
Is.
This.
Craft.
Production.
Is.
Formed.
But.
This.
Craft.
Is.
Obviously.
In.
Now.
Is.
Unable.
To.
Realize.
Because.
The.
Bird.
Is.
A.
Unable.
Craft.
Is.
In.
Space.
That.
Is.
Our.
One.
Disassembly.
Of.
The.
Phoenix.
Is.
A.
Process.
We.
Can.
Use.
This.
Method.
To.
Let.
The.
Audience.
Let.
All.
Customers.
Know.
How.
This.
Is.
Unable.
To.
Understand.
It.
Is.
Unable.
To.
Understand.
This.
Is.
A.
Part.
Of.
Us.
Our.
Society.
But.
That.
Was.
A.
No.
Use.
Any.
Of.
All.
The.
you can also see some horse riding pictures or some historical patterns.
This is actually due to some horse riding sets at the time.
The shape of this skirt is also for convenience.
When you ride a horse, you can have a buckle.
There is a buckle on the waist.
This skirt is fixed to your waist.
Then it's convenient for you to ride a horse.
Then you can see this page.
In fact, we received this historical document from the French Academy.
It has some photos of this costume from different angles.
However, in fact, we will encounter a great difficulty when digitizing.
Most historical costumes do not have the version document at the time.
Because these version documents are very difficult to store.
First of all, it may have some three-dimensional decals at that time.
It is a specific craftsmanship.
Second, it may be difficult to store the paper version paper.
This is why we actually work with various market brands,
universities, and museums.
This is a big problem.
Then we may need to re-transfer all the data that it gives.
All the existing data to re-digitize.
Then re-bring this version back to the present.
This is a specific exhibition page that we made for him at the time.
You can enter their historical story introduction through this interface.
Then there is a small interaction.
You can scroll down and enter the so-called historical page.
Now you can actually see what you're looking at during the exhibition.
Your
doning can be urinated through this.
There's also a relatively modern innovation.
And then you can even scan a QR code to open this actually visual effect of this
Are,
On this website.
Six years ago.
I was talking about how toし
about how to unlock some of these historical values.
Starting from this part, I will introduce some of the directions of our new industry.
It may be more interesting.
First of all, I would like to introduce a project that I just finished last year.
A collaboration with the Roblox platform.
The process of this project is also to use Cloth to do 3D modeling.
The normal design process, we do all the details,
whether it's your name design or some of the materials on your clothes,
including this kind of small pattern design, etc.
After completing all the design,
through the function of UV generation of Cloth,
to guide this model and bring it to other software,
to make a new simplified model,
and then make it reach the standard of a Roblox platform.
I don't know if you know this platform,
just a little bit of background information.
It is actually now in, I think it is, especially in the United States,
and then in Europe, it is actually a very popular one.
It is a concept of the virtual world.
And then many people go to this platform to make friends,
make friends, etc.
It is indeed in the young generation,
like that kind of very young generation,
like 10 years old, maybe younger,
or 16 years old, etc.
This kind of class is a very popular thing.
I once had a collaboration with a friend to talk about this matter.
Because his son is about the age of 10 years old.
And then he said that his son is now in school.
Every time I meet a new friend, I will ask him first.
Do you have this Roblox account?
We almost add each other.
It feels like when we were the youngest,
when I was the youngest,
and then when I was in elementary school,
we added each other QQ.
It's like that.
The difference with this platform is that
you can publish your own design series on it,
and then even sell your own digital clothes.
So this is a concept picture of this series I designed for him.
I call it a defensive battle.
Because this concept,
it is more like I combined some armor design
with some of these,
like this kind of cold ice,
some of these cold ice,
this kind of shape in the era of weapons.
And then I combined it with him.
And then I combined it with a kind of flame,
restoration,
and so on.
Such a concept is in it.
That's a total of three sets of clothes.
These three sets of clothes,
the three pictures you see at the moment,
are the results of my production and rendering in Cloud.
You can see this because you can see
that this is the last time we brought this product to the Roblox platform.
And then he actually has a lot of different styles on the platform.
This kind of small model,
you can choose that kind of square model like a special robot,
and then you can also choose some of the styles that you have customized a little bit.
So this is when we do the test,
we try to put this costume on some of the effects of the different models,
including the effect of different posture and exercise.
At the same time,
you can also use this model to design different versions.
You can see it in the first video,
it has this yellow,
blue,
pink,
and different new versions.
And then this place is another platform.
This is also a cross-border collaboration of the original universe.
I did this project two or three years ago.
I call it digital misculture,
which is the modern culture encountered in digital fashion.
You can understand it like this.
And then this is one of our open call,
which is to collect 10 artists from around the world to work with them,
to digitalize their local cultural costumes,
and bring them to this digital world.
This is also a collaboration with the original universe platform,
which is also a collaboration with the original universe platform,
and then to release an online event with walking shows and interactions.
Here you can see it clearly.
It's a look book.
These ten costumes are a result of the whole display together.
They are from different countries.
The first one is obviously from China.
The second one is from Nigeria.
This characteristic is from its head.
There are many special techniques of wearing beads on it.
It comes from Indian clothing,
Japanese clothing.
This is what we saw just now.
which is a French-made piece of clothing.
All of these different clothing styles
were created through our one-on-one collaboration with artists
or with the Academy of Fine Arts.
This is a gallery.
You can see all of the clothes.
Of course, all of the clothes are made of cloth,
and the effect of the dyeing.
This is an introduction of the exhibition on the Decentraland platform.
We have our own exhibition hall on the platform.
You can see this triangular-shaped outdoor small house.
You can walk into the original universe to see the exhibition.
First, there is a big screen behind it
to play a concept-based walk-through video.
You can also see these static exhibitions in the exhibition hall
and the relevant information behind the exhibition.
This platform allows you to walk around the original universe,
buy land,
interact with each other,
chat with each other, and so on.
Of course, at the same time,
because this is a large event of the Decentraland Fashion Week,
there are many other platforms at the same time.
Other brands even have their own exhibition space
to do some exhibitions in here.
This is another platform.
This is the Decentraland exhibition hall.
On this platform, you can digitalize your own style
and wear these digital clothes.
This is different from the previous one.
The one that is the static exhibition
is more interactive.
You can wear it on your body
and do some DIY style in the exhibition hall
and then watch it.
This is another exhibition hall.
You can see that there is also a map introduction of the exhibition hall
after entering this exhibition hall.
This is from a Digital Fashion Week.
Then you can also see there is also a map introduction of the exhibition hall.
There are also different places for panel talks, like posters on the wall.
You can actually sit in this place and really watch live broadcasts and other online sharing.
This is our small exhibition area.
You can see the same series of costumes as before, but in a different way.
You can also dance or communicate with others.
You can see that the costumes are not as perfect as they used to be.
There are also some variations on people's bodies.
I think this is a kind of digital limitation.
Of course, this is also an interface for real-time communication.
It's becoming more and more...
How do I say it?
It's becoming more and more accurate.
It's becoming more and more effective, but it still takes time.
This is also a project from about three years ago.
And then this place...
Wait a minute, I'm not sure if you can hear the sound.
I just muted the sound.
I think it's better if I introduce it to you.
This is a video I made.
Of course, it is also a video released in Digital Fashion Week.
It is a series of inspiration to honor Alexander McClellan.
Because he once had a fashion show.
It's a model in a firework.
And then there's that kind of self-destruction scene.
This was actually in honor of Saint-Eugène.
It's a French female warrior.
In order to honor him, he made a series.
Here I am also inspired by history.
I made a video with two chapters corresponding to each other.
Now we are looking at the first chapter.
In fact, it is a re-enactment.
Or to honor Saint-Eugène himself.
He killed himself on the battlefield.
And then he fell in the fire.
These scenes.
This model was also made in Cologne.
But this video itself was made in Unreal.
This scene and this animation.
This is the second stage.
The second stage is considered a modern honor.
Then I used this concept to design a whole series of clothes.
And then I did a digital show in it.
It's more like a history of destruction.
The end of a historical story.
And a rebirth of a modern concept.
All the costumes are also sculpted in Cologne.
You can see that many of them are still very delicate.
Of course, this model is looking at it now.
It feels a little fake and a little funny.
Of course, when we are doing these projects.
Time is limited.
Just try as much as possible.
Do your best in a short period of time.
This is a dress with the concept of fire burning.
I didn't play the sound for you.
But the background music of the original video.
It's still a very exciting background music.
And then this is the last one.
It's the ending pose.
An ending pose.
And then this is all of my sharing today.
I am very happy to have this opportunity.
To communicate with everyone.
Say hello.
Hello.